(Leonard:)He's been in bed for two days.
(Penny:)Yeah, probably with a blow-up doll.
(Leonard:)He's not with a...
(Leonard:)Does it really matter who
or what he's with?
The... The guy is devastated.
(Penny:)Oh, please.
How could I possibly devastate Howard?
(Leonard:)Okay, don't take this as a criticism...
...but you do kind of have that
overexposed-to-gamma-rays thing going on.
(Penny:)What does that mean?
(Leonard:)You know. Like, most of the time,
you're the easygoing Bruce Banner.
(Leonard:)But then when you get angry,
you kind of turn into like, you know:
[GROWLS]
(Penny:)I turn into a bear?
(Leonard:)Seriously? Gamma rays? Bruce Banner?
(Leonard:)You didn't get The Incredible Hulk
from that?
(Leonard:)Never mind.
Just... Please, just go talk to him.
Oh, and say what? That I didn't mean it?
Because I meant it.
(Leonard:)Well, maybe you can go at it
from a different angle.
Like, you see a glimmer
of goodness in him...
(Leonard:)...and you only said what you said because
you want to nurture it and make it shine.